I thought I was good at going it alone
Would you prefer to go together?
Place
your finger here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Investigation and Girlfriend"
I don't feel like I'm ever
going to eat that chocolate.
Mom, I now have
an altar at my place
Dreams
Hopes
Lewd Stuff
I'm screwed! Yesterday's date
is playing on loop in my head!
I'm going to look into it.
That was
unfairly cute!!
Everyone else has film masterpieces,
I keep looking
at the chocolate!!
Even opening the box
would be a waste!!
and I have Mizuhara's smile
etched into my brain!
Close your fridge
You're going to
ruin the cooling
Mini-chan told me that
this is what a real bond is.
And it only leads to love,
as everyone else likes to call it.
But think about it this way.
It's my job to be loved.
You say you want me to play it natural,
but it's not like I'm showing
100% of my real self.
There are definitely parts I'm faking.
Telling me you love that version of me
just makes me go, "You're okay with that?"
I mean, you might just be in love
with "Mizuhara Chizuru," not me.
I was ready for the worst when she said
I might be in love with Mizuhara Chizuru.
But she said she was
going to look into it.
What, the moon's volume? No!
She meant how she felt about me.
Hell could freeze over, and I still
wouldn't be yours for real!
That means I'm now
a potential love interest!
Hell has actually frozen over!
Is this all a dream?
Man, I can't!
I Have
Dream
Doing snow angels
out of pure joy
I can't find the words!
It hurts!
My chest
hurts
Look into what?
Whether she loves me, right?
Holy cow! That sounds so good!
Does she have
some kind
of checklist?
She also said she's not exactly
showing 100% of her real self.
Is she gonna look into that, then?
I'm sorry I hid it for so long.
She's going to expose her true self?!
I want you to see me as I truly am.
Mizuhara in the flesh!
I'd love that!
I know I'd
love that 100%!
Letting it go
Pink
I suck! Mizuhara would never!
I'm so messed up!
Quit having
the crudest fantasies!!
Not her of all people!
Yaemori Mini
Good luck! Be spirited!
Today
Yaemori Mini
So, how'd it go?! I need the goss! Give me my fix!
Do you wanna know?
What?!
She said you
might be in love
with
"Mizuhara Chizuru"?
And you just left it there?!
You were supposed to hug her and say,
"I'm in love with Ichinose Chizuru,
who you are on the inside!"
Or don't you?!
What am I, a rugby star?!
I mean,
yeah
And why are you dressed as a nurse?
I know it's
kinda sexy
but it's a
commercial product!!
It happens.
It's
Mizuhara-san,
You know her "investigation"
could go on forever,
and I don't want
to doubt her
and you two might never get
anywhere in the end, right?
You could
say that
W-Well, yeah, that's true...
80-year-old
bachelor (bald)
Some kind
of checklist
You fail this time.
What? That's my 1,208th failure.
C'mon,
pretty please!!
Wah
I've had enough!
I can't take this anymore!
You two will be 80 and still getting
nervous checking each other's Insta!
Asking who you
hung out with and all!
Hey, don't be like that!
Give me some advice!
Yaemori-sama!!
It's just, you were supposed
to score a try there!
There we go with
the rugby again!
But I wanna believe in her.
I wanna believe in that smile.
It made me happy that
she said she'd think about it.
And heck, I want her to be in love
with me if we ever end up dating.
When did you start saying such things?
Aren't you a slave
to your dick?
I thought you didn't care
as long as you got in there.
From the start!!
How can you
cheer me on like that?!
What do you even think I am?!
I thought it
was common
I never thought Mizuhara-san
would go in that direction!
Forget serious,
she's just old-fashioned now!
She could've figured that out
while dating him, too!
Yeahhh, yeah!
But, well, it's very much like her.
Heck, it's just like them both.
That's just
who they are
Well, to be honest,
"You might be in love with 'Mizuhara
Chizuru'" is a sharp observation.
You'll have to show her that no,
it's Ichinose you love.
Yay.
That's quite
the ask
But if she's looking into it,
that means she has to come to you.
Ichinose
The ball's in the heroine's court
for the time being.
Only her beating heart knows
how you two will end up.
I want to ask you straight-up if
there was more to it than that.
I mean, you might just be in love
with "Mizuhara Chizuru," not me.
I may have tried to act too cool there.
No, stop!
Let your worries scatter into the sky!
Mindfulness!
He who rules
over his serotonin
rules over
his life
What, exactly, is she gonna
look into, anyway?
My looks? How fashionable I am?
My grades? My PC's recycle bin?
If she wants to confirm her feelings,
that'll naturally mean
getting to know me better.
That's not good
And then there's that!
Let me kiss you again.
You're welcome to as
many times as you want.
Our physical compatibility!
Yeah, I think I love you.
Right?
Nah, no way!
Kazuya
Not Mizuhara of all people!
I keep slipping into
those fantasies!!
Is that true, though? Like, really?
She might want to, you know?
She probably has lots
of dating experience,
and I keep seeing videos about how
important sexual compatibility is!
Social media
must die!!
Actually, I wonder
what her exes were like.
Hottie
presidents?
I envy them so damn much.
A-Anyway, she said she'd
come to collect the mail.
With that super-cute
LIVE message!
The mail
can go here!
There's no telling when that'll be.
Gotta turn up the heat
so she's not cold!!
Cleanup
I need to be ready at all times!
Cleanup!!
Heya.
H-Hey.
I-It's happening!
Oh, the mail? Here you go.
I think
the coupon
expired,
though!!
Haha!
It came last year, though.
Thanks.
Not that I need it.
Of course...
Gah, she's so cute!
Don't freak out, me! She might
be investigating me already!
But did she really come over
to figure something out?
Is there still a chance she's
just here to pick up the mail?
The cutest bun
in all Japan
Can we have a little chat?
Sure.
Thanks for having me.
She came in! I knew it!
Close it.
Close the door.
Th-That seals the deal!
The investigation is afoot!
D-Done.
She used to avoid being alone in
a room with me like the plague!
Her cheeks
look kinda red, too
She's making it clear that this is
different from the
rental girlfriend thing.
She's trying to get closer to me!
...but it's not like I'm showing
100% of my real self.
She really is going to expose
her natural self
in our very own private investigation!
Can you believe
what I was doing
back there...
Let it go
She'll show me what she
can't show anyone else!
Rent-a-Can't-be-Shown-to
-Anyone-Else-Girlfriend
Are you disappointed in me?
If anything, I love you more now.
Yeah, right.
How she feels about me, that is
She said she's not sure yet.
But there's no doubt she's
going to investigate something.
I feel like I've cleaned up my place
pretty well, but it's not perfect.
Huh?
What? Why's she looking at my bookshelf?
It's pretty much full of aquarium
books and some manga.
All of this
takes place in
1.03 seconds
Ugh, I screwed up!
Maybe I should've thrown
away my old workbooks!
She might think I'm a hopeless hoarder!
To You From Me
Gah! My manga aren't sorted by volume!
Does that make me a
sloppy, unorganized guy?
Wait, why the A/C?
The A/C's bothering her now?
Did I set the temp too high?
She's gonna think I'm wasteful!
Yikes! This is making me so nervous!
Don't look at me
But look at me
My mind's going crazy!
What is this feeling?
It's like her eyes are stripping me naked.
Don't look at me.
She's judging every nook and cranny of me!
But look at me.
I might not
meet her standards
Come to think of it,
it's possible I might fail
this investigation, too!
I thought long and hard about it,
but you get two points.
That'll actually hurt me bigtime!
No!
Please, no!
Anything but that, please!
Hey.
Are you listening?
Can I sit down?
O-Oh, go right ahead.
I'm so
inconsiderate!!
I keep wasting
my brain's CPU cycles
whenever I'm with her!!
You should've told her that, fool!
Exhibit A: Wholesome Investigation
She's here for an investigation!
I should serve tea and entertain her!
Huh?
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Wha?!
Wait, she's sitting down there?
Why there? Why so distant?
In the corner
of the room
Is she still wary of me? Or does she
not want to sit anywhere close to me?
And why does she seem kinda subdued?
Like she's feeling awkward or
uncomfortable about something.
Like a cat that doesn't belong here.
Is this part of her investigation?
I have no frickin' idea!
Let's go over our situation a little.
Personally, I still feel like
I'm doing Ruka-chan wrong.
Considering her feelings,
it wouldn't be good if she
found out what was going on.
Huh?
Ruka-chan?
Close the door
Oh, so that's why she was so cautious.
Yeah, if Ruka-chan found out,
we'd be on a highway to hell.
Why are you giving him
an optimistic response?!
You're just a rental girlfriend!
What exactly are you
investigating my boyfriend for?!
I-It's okay. She said she was busy
with homework tonight.
I see.
How's it going with her lately?
It's been a year and a half now.
A lot's happened lately,
so I want to know the status.
The status? It's status quo... I guess.
Same as always.
I mean, things got a bit
rocky after Hawaiians,
but we're back to normal now.
Oh.
I can see why she'd want to know.
She's the one who hooked us up,
I'm not done here!
and look where that ended up.
I did tell her I wanted to break up.
Just before the Hawaiians trip.
What?
I knew my answer already,
so it didn't feel right
to let things drag on.
But she said she knew all that
and still didn't want to end it.
That's so like her.
The perfect response
Y-Yeah.
Her feelings for you
must be the real deal.
I don't want to hurt her
any more than I already have.
Given the risk of her finding out,
it's a bad idea for us to
be meeting up like this.
Mizuhara...
Yeah, that makes sense.
She takes these things seriously.
Heck, she even ghosted me
for months for Ruka-chan.
So even if she does try
to figure things out,
it won't be that easy for
our relationship to change.
sad...
But you can trust me.
I said I'd look into it, but I don't
really know how to go about it.
I know I'm being kind of childish
about this whole thing.
And I'm aware I'm being unfair
by putting things off.
But like I said, I'm not going
to sweep this under the rug.
I will figure out a solution
for this situation we're in.
I know it's kinda silly, but could you
let me off with that for now?
Oh... Even she doesn't know
how to go about it.
But she's still taking it seriously.
Even as she feels guilt over Ruka-chan,
she's giving me a chance.
Even as she feels guilt over her job,
I just can't hold it in anymore.
I really do love her!
Are you free after this?
Huh?
Why?
Do you need me for something?
Whoa, I totally went off the rails!
When will I learn?
I'm so stupid!
The Loveliest ♥
I figured I could help if she
didn't know how to go about it!
I don't want her
to leave yet!
All because I wanted to get closer to her!
My inner voice
leaked out!
And I do! I do want to
get closer to her for real!
What have I got?
What can we do?
W...
Wanna watch some WeTube with me?
What?
Do you
have recs
or something?
Where'd that come from?
D'oh! "Where did that come from" is right!
She knows I'm just
throwing shit at the wall!
She can tell I'm just grasping
at straws to get closer to her!
You're in the literature
department, right?
I wanted you
to see it
I found a channel that does
cool deep dives on Japanese lit.
I didn't find shit, though!
I don't watch
that stuff
But I can probably find
something if I search for it!
At least a couple
of channels
Is this working?
She's not weirded out?
Because I'm
trying too hard
Sure, that's fine.
Woohoo! We're in!
G-Give me a sec. I'll set it up.
Wait, what was it called?
I think it started with a "Ta."
Run a search, filter the results,
and pick something that feels right.
If I do all that fast enough,
it'll be like I knew all along.
I can say,
"Yeah, that's the one"
I know
I can do this
How desperate are you?
What? She's so close.
So close. I mean, it makes sense.
We're gonna watch WeTube.
This would
happen
She smells so nice, though!
I can't, I can't! Don't come any closer!
She'll hear my heart racing!
Wait, I need to focus right now!
I gotta find a good video in an instant!
Koronemaru's
Mt. Rushmore of Bras
Top 5 Recommended Underwear
Crazy
push-ups
Damn, it's all Koronemaru!
My feed's full of
Yaemori-san's
(slightly spicy) videos!!!
N-No way! This can't be happening!
This makes me look like a
creepo perving on another girl!
I'm just a cheating scumbag!!
I-It's not what it looks like.
She's really working hard on her WeTube.
I got hooked
So I checked out her channel,
on her videos!
and it turns out her videos
are actually great.
Look at
him panic
What are you saying?
Anybody would get curious and
check out their neighbor's channel.
Huh? You're okay with that?
I'm allowed to watch her?
What an angel...
I think I want to watch that one.
Which one?
Koronemaru's
Mt. Rushmore of Bras
Top 5 Recommended Underwear
Crazy
push-ups
The one on the top,
with the underwear recommendations.
Wait, what? Underwear?!
Okay, then.
Yeah, go ahead.
Hit play
This one even has wires on the sides.
The push-up effect is crazy.
I had
no idea
Wow, she knows her stuff.
Maybe I should
try it out
What's more, the padding is really soft.
Whoa, hang on. Are we really
talking about underwear here?
Is this
really okay?!
She's talking about
trying it out and stuff?!
We're just talking about
underwear like it's no big deal!
Damn, what's going on here?
It's just me and Mizuhara...
watching something at my place...
It adds, like, two cup sizes!
Mini-chan's so funny.
It's like she's my girlfriend.
I want to cry
Okay, I should get going.
The stage play I mentioned
before opens soon.
I need to double-check the
script tonight for rehearsal.
Oh, yeah?
Right, she's a super hard worker.
And she must be as busy
as ever with her acting work.
I'll walk you.
I live next door.
And there's the whole Ruka-chan
thing to worry about, too.
But she still took time out
for me in the middle of all that.
...you two might never get
anywhere in the end, right?
You're wrong, Yaemori-san.
Mizuhara's always been good to me.
There's no way she'd just lead me on!
I'll look into it.
There's something I need to say to her.
Thanks for having me.
Listen, Mizuhara!
What?
After you said you'd look into it,
I thought about it a bunch, too.
I don't know if my feelings
will get through,
but I want you to know
this if nothing else.
I'll wait for you.
Even if it takes ten or twenty years,
I'll wait as long as you want.
Until the day comes when you're
ready to tell me you love me,
I'll always be waiting.
Thanks for making time for me tonight.
What are you even saying?
You've got your
family business
to think about, too
You'll be past marriageable age.
But don't worry.
I'll give it a real shot.
Goodnight.
Spring was nearly upon us.
Rawr!
Wow, Mizuhara-san! You and Master
watched one of my videos together?
Yeah, it was great.
I couldn't stop watching.
Aw, you're making me blush.
I'll go ahead and profile one
of your bras next, then.
I said no last time!
That was panties! I thought I might
have a shot with a bra instead!
No! No shot!
Forget that! Next time
on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Bra and...
...Girlfriend."
Wait, after all that,
we get this episode title?!
Can't wait for the next episode!
"Bra and Girlfriend"